<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-05-11T11:27:59-07:00</updated><id>https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site//</id><title type="html">Sarah</title><author><name>Sarah</name><uri>https://esimonian.github.io/</uri></author><entry><title type="html">Illustrator Script: Export Artboards @2x</title><link href="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/design/2017/01/28/illustrator-script-export-artboars/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Illustrator Script: Export Artboards @2x" /><published>2017-01-28T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2017-01-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/design/2017/01/28/illustrator-script-export-artboars</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/design/2017/01/28/illustrator-script-export-artboars/">&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col s12 m6&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Exporting .ai artboards at dual resolution and renaming the subsequent files can be a big pain, so I recently scoured the internet for a script to do it for me. Nothing I found quite worked, so I modified and refactored one to meet my needs.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col s12 m6&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/sarah-site/assets/images/illustrator-script-post.png&quot; alt=&quot;Illustrator Script&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What it does&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The script exports all artboards to the directory of your choice at 100% and 200% scaling. It also names them in the form [filename]-[artboard name].png and [filename]-[artboard name]@2x.png.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will also ignore locked layers so background or guide layers won’t get in your way every time you want to export something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Example output&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;File name: dashboard icons.ai
Artboard names: create, refresh, send
Exported images:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dashboard-icons-create.png&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dashboard-icons-create*@*2x.png&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dashboard-icons-refresh.png&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dashboard-icons-refresh@2x.png&quot;&gt;dashboard-icons-refresh@2x.png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dashboard-icons-send.png&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dashboard-icons-send@2x.png&quot;&gt;dashboard-icons-send@2x.png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How to install&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download the script here&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Put the file in Illustrator’s scripts directory: Adobe Illustrator/Presets/Scripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restart Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How to use&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the .ai file you wish to export&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure the layers you wish to export are unlocked&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute via File &amp;gt; Scripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How to configure (optional)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want specific syntax in your filenames or a hardcoded export directory, open the file in a text editor and review the comments. I’ve created several places where you can easily configure this script to fit your needs like so:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/sarah-site/assets/images/script-instructions-example.png&quot; alt=&quot;Script instructions&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Special thanks&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I modified this script from a version by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com&quot;&gt;Hot Apps Factory&lt;/a&gt;which exports and names compatibly with Android apps as well as iOS. That script is itself an improvement on Herculano Campos’ script.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sarah</name><uri>https://esimonian.github.io/</uri></author><category term="illustrator" /><category term="artboards" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Video Blog</title><link href="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/popular/2017/01/04/video-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Video Blog" /><published>2017-01-04T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2017-01-04T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/popular/2017/01/04/video-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/popular/2017/01/04/video-blog/">&lt;div class=&quot;videoWrapper&quot;&gt;
  &lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ScMzIvxBSi4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sarah</name><uri>https://esimonian.github.io/</uri></author><category term="video" /><category term="responsive" /></entry><entry><title type="html">UX vs. UI Design</title><link href="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/ux/2015/02/23/ux-vs-ui-design/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="UX vs. UI Design" /><published>2015-02-23T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2015-02-23T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/ux/2015/02/23/ux-vs-ui-design</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/ux/2015/02/23/ux-vs-ui-design/">&lt;p&gt;Many people use these terms interchangeably, but they are actually quite different and imply different skillsets among their practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UI stands for User Interface, but it could be described better as “the hardware or software through which a user interacts with a product.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UX stands for User eXperience, but it could be more completely described as “what the user experiences throughout the entirety of his interaction with every aspect of a product.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A simple example&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of your TV. You probably interact with it via the remote control and maybe also some menus in the TV’s software. Both the physical control and the menus could be called the TV’s user interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The user experience of your TV, though, encompasses a much broader set of things: how hard it was to unbox, whether the manual was easy to understand, how it looks in your living room, how many video inputs/outputs it has, whether the ports are easy to access, how long you had to wait on hold when you called the manufacturer to ask a question about it, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly the remote control and the software menus are part of your experience with your TV. And in that same way, user interface design is a part of user experience design. Although people and roles vary, UX designers tend to be jacks of all trades while UI designers usually specialize in creating interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some practical examples&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A typical UI designer might try to answer questions like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What should our sign-up form look like? Should all the inputs be visible at once, or should some of them be hidden and then only appear after the user completes the first one? How should we inform the user if an email address isn’t valid or his preferred username has already been taken? Should the box get outlined in red, or should we put a little X next to it?
On the product dashboard, what information should be displayed by default? How can we indicate to the user that items can be removed from the dashboard? Should we use an X icon in the corner of each item, or some other icon? Should the X icon always be visible on each item, or should it only appear on hover?
Where should the navigation links appear on our website, the top or the side? Should the link to the contact page actually say “Contact,” or should it say “Email us” or “Support”? When a user filters our search results, how should we display which filters are applied? Does the user remove a filter by hitting “Back” or by clicking a tiny X next to each applied filter?
A typical UX designer might consider some of the UI questions above, but he or she would also try to answer other questions about the product:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When sending emails to the customer, whom should the sender be – the name of the company? The name of the CSR? If a customer replies to an automated message, what happens to it? Do we just have a no-reply address, or does that message get sent to a person somewhere?
Which is more important to launch first, feature X or feature Y?
What should the structure of our website be? What pages should it have, and how should the user navigate between them?
Should we spend time creating spectacular visual design, or is it better to work on improving feature X instead?
Why do users buy our product? Why don’t they buy our product?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sarah</name><uri>https://esimonian.github.io/</uri></author><category term="UX" /><category term="UI Design" /><category term="Design" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/jekyll/2015/02/03/welcome-to-jekyll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2015-02-03T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2015-02-03T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/jekyll/2015/02/03/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/jekyll/2015/02/03/welcome-to-jekyll/">&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll find this post in your &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory - edit this post and re-build
(or run with the &lt;code&gt;-w&lt;/code&gt; switch) to see your changes! To add new posts, simply add
a file in the &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention:
YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve also added a lot of different settings for &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/vmg/redcarpet&quot;&gt;Redcarpet&lt;/a&gt;,
including being able to &lt;sup&gt;superscript,&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;u&gt;underline&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;mark&gt;highlight&lt;/mark&gt;,
&lt;del&gt;strikethrough&lt;/del&gt;, and footnotes.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn1&quot; rel=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; It even automatically makes links into
URLs: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;www.jekyllrb.com&lt;/a&gt; and you can put multiple underscores in words without
them leaning all over the place: this_word_has_underscores. It&amp;rsquo;ll also make your
quotes look nice, like this: &amp;ldquo;hoho&amp;rdquo;, your dashes and hypens will be dashing too:
&amp;mdash;/&amp;ndash;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home/&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of
Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll&amp;rsquo;s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;

&lt;li id=&quot;fn1&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who are quite handy&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;#fnref1&quot; rev=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sarah</name><uri>https://esimonian.github.io/</uri></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="learning" /><category term="testing" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Why you shouldn’t trust your users</title><link href="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/popular/2013/01/07/why-shouldnt-trust-your-users/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why you shouldn't trust your users" /><published>2013-01-07T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2013-01-07T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/popular/2013/01/07/why-shouldnt-trust-your-users</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://esimonian.github.io/sarah-site/popular/2013/01/07/why-shouldnt-trust-your-users/">&lt;p&gt;Your users are like your children. They have opinions and hopes and entitlements and tantrums. Sometimes their demands are reasonable (&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m thirsty&amp;rdquo;) or unreasonable (&amp;ldquo;I want brownies for breakfast every day!&amp;rdquo;). If you want to create a great experience for your user, it&amp;rsquo;s your job to figure out which requests are really in their best interest. They might think they know, and sometimes they&amp;rsquo;re correct &amp;ndash; but like parents, sometimes you need to protect them from the times that they&amp;rsquo;re wrong. (And conveniently, protecting them also protects you and your business.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The parable of the pine nuts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week I went to Whole Foods to get some pine nuts for a kale salad. In case you&amp;rsquo;re not aware, pine nuts are not cheap &amp;ndash; the smallest bag they had was $8.99 for what appeared to be 1.5 cups. Of course, one salad only takes a smattering of nuts, so spending $8.99 on it seemed gratuitously spendy. (Especially since I&amp;rsquo;m the only one in my apartment who even eats salad in the first place.) But I really did want that salad &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s the most delicious recipe &amp;ndash; so I thought to myself &amp;ldquo;Perhaps I can justify this pricey purchase if the nuts will keep for a long time. Then, even if don&amp;rsquo;t have another salad for two months, they&amp;rsquo;ll still be good.&amp;rdquo; This logic seemed sound and also allowed me to get my nuts guilt-free, so I looked all over the bag for something indicating how long they&amp;rsquo;d last after opening &amp;ndash; to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Whole Foods employees are almost always really knowledgeable, so I started looking around for someone to ask. I wandered around from one aisle to the next, trying in vain to find someone. Eventually I found a fellow who had no idea how long pine nuts last, but he determinedly escorted me around the store, from employee to employee, each one saying &amp;ldquo;Oh, I bet Dan would know,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Ask Clyde in the back.&amp;rdquo; Down the rabbit hole we went, and at the end of our trek there was a very nice man who told me that pine nuts can last months without any ill effects. Great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then as I began to walk away &amp;ndash; now in a small hurry after the lengthy tour of Whole Foods employees &amp;ndash; the man added &amp;ldquo;You know, if the bag is too big&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; I was a little impatient at being called back, since I now had my answer and wanted to get on my way. But I&amp;rsquo;m a nice person, so I put on a polite smile and turned back to face him. He continued: &amp;ldquo;If the bag is too big, you could just get them from the bulk foods aisle. Then you can buy however much you need.&amp;rdquo; I nodded and thanked him, thinking &amp;ldquo;Yes, I know how grocery stores work.&amp;rdquo; But it was only as I was walking away again that I realized that that was exactly what I needed; in my single-minded efforts to create my own solution, I had forgotten my ultimate goal. So I bought half a cup of pine nuts at a much more reasonable price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The critical reader might point out that Whole Foods made less money off of me than if I&amp;rsquo;d bought the $8.99 bag. Maybe so. Or maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll buy a lot more kale and pine nuts from them in the future now that I know I don&amp;rsquo;t have to run the risk of wasting it. (I&amp;rsquo;d be very surprised if my lifetime customer value to Whole Foods hasn&amp;rsquo;t increased after this.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;So how can I use this in my business?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most important thing to understand from this post is that you can&amp;rsquo;t always trust your customers. Not because they&amp;rsquo;re liars, but because they&amp;rsquo;re really susceptible to getting trapped in their own context. Really, we&amp;rsquo;re all susceptible to that in all aspects of life - it&amp;rsquo;s just that in business we&amp;rsquo;re a lot more incentivized to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the surface, of course, the question &amp;ldquo;how long will this food last?&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem very similar to &amp;ldquo;can I buy a smaller amount?&amp;rdquo; This Whole Foods employee was able to see past the question to my underlying goal beneath it &amp;ndash; even though I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really aware of that goal anymore. That&amp;rsquo;s a very impressive UX feat, and it shows that this fellow really understands his customers. On the other hand, many people understand the needs of shoppers in a grocery store &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly a new business model. The tricky part is learning how to gain that understanding when your users&amp;rsquo; goals aren&amp;rsquo;t as obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what can you do? There are lots of great ways to conduct user research that can mitigate this effect, such as writing surveys carefully and well. (See my guide on writing effective user surveys.) But every business is different, and the best way to get user feedback will vary from case to case. (If there were a one-size-fits-all solution to this, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a problem anymore.) Hiring a user experience expert is a great first step, though. Preferably one with a solid understanding of user research. As a matter of fact, I&amp;rsquo;m looking for work myself! Send me an email &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;d love to talk about your company&amp;rsquo;s needs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sarah</name><uri>https://esimonian.github.io/</uri></author><category term="user experience design" /><category term="user research" /></entry></feed>
